[{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>The miscreant tried to sow seeds of ----- among members.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["Accord","Discord","Concord","Alliance"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"null"},{"question":"<p><b>Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/b><br><\/p>\r\n<p><span style=\"letter-spacing: .7pt;\"><b>The play was performed well and the ___ acclaimed.<\/b><\/span><\/p>","options":["Congregation","Audience","Crowd","Crew"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>His writing is as illegible as his voice is ___.<\/b><\/p>","options":["Harsh","Unbearable","Inaudible","Inarticulate"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>Following his --- from the University he decided to set up a poultry.<\/b><\/p>","options":["Dismissal","Dismissed","Dismiss","Dismissing"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<h4><span style=\"font-size: 14px;\"><b>Choose the option that best fills the gap(s).<\/b><\/span><\/h4><h4><span style=\"font-size: 14px;\"><b>The thief ___ my house and stole my television.<\/b><\/span><\/h4>","options":["Broke into","Broke down","Broke in","Broke off"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<h4>Choose from options A- D the phrase or statement which has the nearest in terpret tion to the underlined part of the initial statement.<\/h4>\r\n<p>He seemed to have <span style=\"text-decoration: underline;\">gone off the rails<\/span><\/p>","options":["He stopped travelling by rail","He has stopped working with the rails","He fell unto the rails","He is behaving in a very strange way"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><b>Choose the option OPPOSITE in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.<\/b><\/p>\r\n<p><b>It is generally believed that <span style=\"text-decoration: underline;\"><i>misers<\/i><\/span> are not loved by many<\/b><\/p>","options":["Spenders","Spendthrifts","Hoarders","Thieves"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option OPPOSITE in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><b>My  sister\u2019s  secondary   education   was  <i><u>solid<\/u> <\/i>and   this  affected   her   university<\/b><\/p>","options":["Ground","Shaky","Weak","Sordid"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option OPPOSITE in meaning to the word(s) or phrase in italics.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><b>There has been some <i><u>turmoil<\/u> <\/i>on the political front in the last few<\/b><\/p>","options":["Quite","Turbulence","Realignment","Discomfiture"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<h4><span style=\"font-size: 14px;\"><b>Choose the option that best fills the gap(s).<\/b><\/span><\/h4><h4><span style=\"font-size: 14px;\"><b>Being a nursing mother ___ Business Management, Bukola cannot always attend the evening.<\/b><\/span><\/h4>","options":["who had read","having read","reading","and who read"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>He was the ___ in Nigeria.<\/b><\/p>","options":["Greatest player ever","Ever greater player","Player ever greatest","Greater player ever"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>The lecturer insisted ___ the assignment.<\/b><\/p>","options":["By my completing","On my completing","To my completing","For my completing"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>You had better ___ the problem, otherwise, it will remain unsolved.<\/b><\/p>","options":["Faced","Face","Been facing","To face"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>You do not have any choice, you ___ take it or leave.<\/b><\/p>","options":["Neither","Whether","Whither","Either"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><b>It is true that Janet cannot speak English as fluently as her sister -----<\/b><\/p>","options":["Do","Does","Can do","Speaks"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><b>Charlie declares that she ------ married three times<\/b><\/p>","options":["Had been","Has Been","Have been","Has being"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><b>The man asked his wife if anyone called ----- his absence<\/b><\/p>","options":["By","For","At","During"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>I have made a lot of friends ---- I entered into this school<\/b><\/p>","options":["When","Since","While","As"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>A suggestion has&nbsp;been made&nbsp;that&nbsp;any civil&nbsp;servant&nbsp;found guilty&nbsp;of official corruption should be ___.<\/b><\/p>","options":["Explained","Expressed","Exposed","Expelled"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>After each of the following sentences, a list of possible interpretations of the whole or part of the sentence is given. Choose the interpretation which you consider appropriate for each sentence.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><b>The lesson had hardly begun when the light went off.<br><\/b><\/p>","options":["Did not start before the light went off","Started after the light went  off","Started shortly before the light went off","Still lying where it was found"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>After each of the following sentences, a list of possible interpretations of the whole or part of the sentence is given. Choose the interpretation which you consider appropriate for each sentence.<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><b>The teacher said that the book ought to have been left where it was.<\/b><\/p><p><b> The above sentence shows that the book was...<\/b><\/p>\r\n<p>&nbsp;<\/p>","options":["Left where it was found","Removed from where it was found","Never removed at all","Still lying where it was found"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"Select year"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the word which will best complete this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>It is true that Janet cannot speak English as fluently as her sister ...<\/strong><\/p>","options":["do","does","can do","speaks"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the word which will best complete this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>Charlie declares that she ... married three times.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["had been","has been","have been","has being"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the word which will best complete this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>The man asked his wife if anyone called ... his absence.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["by","for","at","during"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the word which will best complete this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>I have made a lot of friends ... I entered into this school.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["when","since","while","as"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the word which will best complete this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>A suggestion has been made that any civil servant found guilty of official corruption should be ...<\/strong><\/p>","options":["explained","expressed","exposed","expelled"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the interpretation which you consider appropriate for this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>The lesson had hardly begun when the light went off.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["did not start before the light went off","started after the light went off","started shortly before the light went off","still lying where it was found"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the interpretation which you consider appropriate for this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>The teacher said that the book ought to have been left where it was found. The above sentence that the book was...<\/strong><\/p>","options":["left where it was found","removed from where it was found","never removed at all","still lying where it was found"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the appropriate word to fill the gap in this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>I am waiting ... a good opportunity to travel abroad.<\/strong><\/p>","options":["of","during","by","for"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the appropriate word to fill the gap in this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>The mother divided the oranges ... her three sons<\/strong><\/p>","options":["for","by","to","between"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the appropriate word to fill the gap in this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>He acted as counsel ... the defendant<\/strong><\/p>","options":["for","to","with","from"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the appropriate word to fill the gap in this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>Never you point accusing finger ... me<\/strong><\/p>","options":["to","on","for","at"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the appropriate word to fill the gap in this sentence<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>He needn't start yet, ... he?<\/strong><\/p>","options":["could","couldn't","need","needn't"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option that best complete the gaps<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>While I am the ... child in the family, John is the ...<\/strong><\/p>","options":["oldest\/youngest","eldest\/youngest","eldest\/younger","senior\/junior"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option that best completes the gap<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>We have ... fruits in the rainy season<\/strong><\/p>","options":["many","several","a little","very many"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><strong>Choose the option that best completes the gap<\/strong><\/p>\r\n<p><strong>Everyone of the chiefs ... a car<\/strong><\/p>","options":["is owning","owns","have","own"],"answerIndex":2,"examYear":"2015"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>I am waiting --------- a good opportunity to travel abroad<\/b><\/p>","options":["of","during","by","for"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2013"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>The mother divided the oranges ----- her three sons<\/b><\/p>","options":["for","by","to","among"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2013"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>He acted as counsel --- the defendant<\/b><\/p>","options":["for","to","with","from"],"answerIndex":1,"examYear":"2013"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>Never you point accusing finger ---- me!<\/b><\/p>","options":["to","on","for","at"],"answerIndex":4,"examYear":"2013"},{"question":"<p><span style=\"font-weight: bolder;\">Choose the option that best fills the gap(s)<\/span><br><\/p>\r\n<p><b>He needn\u2019t start yet, ___ he?<\/b><\/p>","options":["could","couldn\u2019t","need","needn\u2019t"],"answerIndex":3,"examYear":"2013"}]